toovia.com 2016-03-13

# Privacy Policy | TOOVIA

Welcome to TOOVIA.com ("TOOVIA", "we", "us", or "our"). TOOVIA provides an easy and fun way for you to plan and coordinate your trips – whether it is personal or a group. Simply register, logon, and drag & drop the hotels, tours, and any other TOOVIA offerings that you like, and customize a trip that your family, friends, or colleagues can simply sign on and join … voilà! Your customized group trip is ready – no hassle, no fuss! 

This is our Privacy Policy explaining how and what we and some of the companies we work with do in collecting, using, sharing, and protecting information in relation to our mobile services, web site, and any software provided on or in connection with TOOVIA services (collectively, the "Service"), and your choices about the collection and use of your information. 

By using our Service you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to make bookings, post content, including photos, comments, and other materials ("User Content" or “Your Content”), to the Service and to share User Content publicly. This means that other Users may search for, see, use, or share any of your User Content that you make publicly available through the Service, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our User Agreement. 

However, you do control how you want to share and distribute your User Content by adjusting your privacy settings in your TOOVIA Profile. You can control how you share information with those third- party applications and websites through your Profile Settings. We will not share your information with advertisers without your consent. We allow advertisers to select characteristics of users they want to show their advertisements to and we use the information users share with us to serve those advertisements. 

Our Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Service ("Users"). 

> 1\. WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM USERS

We collect the following types of information. 

  * Your username, password, and e-mail address when you register for a TOOVIA account.
  * Profile information that you provide for your TOOVIA Profile (e.g.: first and last name, picture, phone number, and other personal information you want to provide). This information helps you or others “find” you on TOOVIA.
  * User Content (e.g.: bookings, trip planner, photos, comments, and other materials) that you post to the Service.
  * We may also request information about your hotel room preferences, frequent flyer membership, and car rental program information. You can choose not to provide information to us, but in general some information about you is required in order for you to register; book travel; complete a traveler profile; participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes; ask us a question; or initiate other transactions on TOOVIA.
  * Communications between you and TOOVIA. For example, we may send you Service-related emails (e.g.: account verification, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical, and security notices). Note that you may not opt out of Service-related e-mails. However, you may opt-out of communications from advertisers.

  * If you choose, you can use our “Invite Friends” features to locate other people with TOOVIA accounts either through (i) your contacts list, (ii) third-party social media sites or (iii) through a search of names on TOOVIA.
  * If you choose to find your friends through (i) your device's contacts list, then TOOVIA will access your contacts list to determine whether or not someone associated with your contact is using TOOVIA.
  * If you choose to find your friends through a (ii) third-party social media site, then you will be prompted to set up a link to the third-party service and you understand that any information that such service may provide to us will be governed by this Privacy Policy.
  * If you choose to find your friends (iii) through a search of names or usernames on TOOVIA then simply type a name to search and we will perform a search on our Service.

**Note about Travel Companion Information:** Our Partners may allow you to make reservations for someone else. Please visit their respective privacy policies and their Terms and Conditions before making any bookings for another. Please also make sure to obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing TOOVIA or our Partners with their personal information and travel preferences. 

  * We also may periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated entities, business partners, and other independent third-party sources and add it to our account information. Examples of information we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and demographic information.
  * If you sign up for TOOVIA using your social media account, link your TOOVIA account to your social media account, or use certain other TOOVIA social media features, we may access information about you via that social media provider in accordance with the provider's policies. The information may include your name, email address, profile picture, gender, list of friends, and other information that you authorize us to receive. Depending on the privacy settings of you and your friends, we may access information that you provide to a social media provider regarding your respective locations ("Location Data") to provide you with relevant content. Please note that your Location Data may also be shared with your friends on a social media provider in accordance with your privacy settings for that social media provider.

  * We use analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your device or our Service, including the web pages you visit, add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information with analytics information from other Users so that it cannot reasonably be used to identify any particular individual User.

  * Depending on how you're accessing our products, we may use "cookies" (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our website, unique to your TOOVIA account or your browser), or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies, we may use "session" cookies (that last until you close your browser) or "persistent" cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). For example, we may use cookies to store your language preferences or other TOOVIA settings so you don't have to set them up every time you visit TOOVIA.

  * Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to access (i.e.: visit) a web page or app. It can also be provided when the content of the webpage or app is downloaded to your browser or device.
  * In using our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information, including your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. We may also collect similar information from emails sent to our Users which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Service.

  * When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone to access our Service, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your device, and/or remotely store one or more "device identifiers.” Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by TOOVIA.
  * A device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third party partner about how you browse and use the Service and may help us or others provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.

  * Metadata is usually technical data that is associated with User Content. For example, Metadata can describe how, when and by whom a piece of User Content was collected and how that content is formatted.
  * Users can add or may have Metadata added to their User Content including a hashtag (e.g.: to mark keywords when you post a photo or check-in), geotag (e.g.: to mark your location to a photo or check-in), comments or other data. This makes your User Content more searchable by others and more interactive. If you geotag your photo or tag your photo using other's APIs, then, your latitude and longitude will be stored with the photo and searchable (e.g.: through a location or map feature) if your photo is made public by you in accordance with your privacy settings.

> 2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

In addition to some of the specific uses of information we describe in this Privacy Policy, we may use information that we receive to: 

  * help you efficiently access your information after you sign in
  * manage your account, including trips purchased and providing travel notifications, travel confirmation, and other updates
  * remember information so you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Service;
  * provide personalized content and information to you and others, which could include online ads or other forms of marketing, as well as measure interest in and improve our products, services, and website, and notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you
  * provide, improve, test, and monitor the effectiveness of our Service
  * solicit information from you, including through surveys
  * develop and test new products and features
  * provide you with the products and services you request
  * customize your experience with TOOVIA and reward you as part of any reward and recognition program you choose to join
  * monitor metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns
  * diagnose or fix technology problems and/or respond to your questions and comments, and resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and enforce our User Agreement and Community Rules
  * automatically update the TOOVIA application on your device, TOOVIA or other Users may run contests, special offers, or other events or activities ("Events") on the Service. If you do not want to participate in an Event, do not use the particular Metadata (i.e. hashtag or geotag) associated with that Event.

Currently, we do not keep sensitive billing information (such as cardholder name, credit card number, and expiration date) on TOOVIA. Such sensitive information may be required when booking your trip through our partner providers, please review their privacy policy and Terms of Use prior to submitting your sensitive information. 

> 3\. SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION

We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside TOOVIA without your consent, except as noted in this Policy. Be aware that when you click on links in TOOVIA, you may leave the TOOVIA site, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. So, we encourage you to read their privacy statements. 

Parties with whom we may share your information:

  * We may share User Content and your information (including but not limited to, information from cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data, and usage data) with businesses that are legally part of the same group of companies that TOOVIA is part of, or that become part of that group ("Affiliates"). Affiliates may use this information to help provide, understand, and improve the Service (including by providing analytics) and Affiliates' own services (including by providing you with better and more relevant experiences). But these Affiliates will honor the choices you make about your privacy through your TOOVIA Profile.
  * We may share your information with suppliers, such as hotel, airline, car rental, tours, and activity providers, who fulfill your travel reservations. Throughout TOOVIA, all services provided by a third- party supplier are indicated. We do not share your email address with these suppliers unless they need it to fulfill the travel reservation you have made on TOOVIA, and we restrict their use of this information to that purpose. All payment information submitted through TOOVIA to suppliers will not be stored in TOOVIA and such payment information will be transmitted via Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). Please note that we do not place limitations on our suppliers' use or disclosure of your non-payment related personal information. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any travel supplier whose products you purchase through TOOVIA. Please note that suppliers also may contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about you, facilitate your travel reservation, or respond to a review you may submit.
  * We also may share your information as well as information from tools like cookies, log files, and device identifiers and location data, with third-party organizations that help us provide the Service to you ("Service Providers"), for example, a security consultant to identify Spam. Our Service Providers will be given access to your information as is reasonably necessary to provide the Service under reasonable confidentiality terms.
  * If you were referred to TOOVIA from another site (e.g.: through a link you clicked on another site that directed you to TOOVIA), we may share some information about you with that referring website. We have not placed limitations on the referring websites use of your personal information and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that referred you to TOOVIA.
  * In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us – please see Responding to legal requests and preventing harm below 
  * When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company or this website, our customers, or others; and in connection with our User Agreement, Community Rules, and other agreements. 
  * In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
  * We may remove parts of data that can identify you and share anonymized data with other parties. We may also combine your information with other information in a way that it is no longer associated with you and share that aggregated information.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information. 

Parties with whom you may choose to share your User Content:

  * Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings that you set. To change your privacy settings on the Service, please change your profile setting. Once you have shared User Content or made it public, that User Content may be re-shared by others.
  * Subject to your profile and privacy settings, any User Content that you make public is searchable by other Users.
  * If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service.

What happens in the event of a change of control:

  * If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of TOOVIA or our assets to another organization (e.g.: in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation), your information such as name, email address, User Content, and any other information collected through the Service may be among the items sold or transferred. You will continue to own your User Content. The buyer or transferee will have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy.

Responding to legal requests and preventing harm:

  * We may access, preserve, and share your information in response to a legal request (like a search warrant, court order, or subpoena) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of the United States where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction, affects users in that jurisdiction, and is consistent with internationally recognized standards.
  * We may also access, preserve, and share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to: detect, prevent, and address fraud and other illegal activity; to protect ourselves, you, and others, including as part of investigations; and to prevent death or imminent bodily harm.
  * Information we receive about you may be accessed, processed, and retained for an extended period of time when it is the subject of a legal request or obligation, governmental investigation, or investigations concerning possible violations of our terms or policies, or otherwise to prevent harm.

> 4\. HOW WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION

Storage and Processing:

  * Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which TOOVIA, its Affiliates, or Service Providers maintain facilities.
  * TOOVIA, its Affiliates, or Service Providers may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.
  * By registering for and using the Service you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or to any other country in which TOOVIA, its Affiliates, or Service Providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
  * We use commercially reasonable safeguards to help keep the information collected through the Service secure and take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. However, TOOVIA cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to TOOVIA or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed.
  * Please do your part to help us. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to emails between you and TOOVIA, at all times. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes the social media services you connect to TOOVIA make to their services. We are not responsible for the functionality, privacy, or security measures of any other organization.

> 5\. YOUR CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION

Your account information and profile/privacy settings:

  * Update your account at any time by logging in and changing your TOOVIA Profile.
  * Unsubscribe from email communications from us by clicking on the "unsubscribe link" provided in such communications. As noted above, you may not opt out of Service-related communications (e.g.: account verification, purchase and billing confirmations, and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Service, and technical and security notices).
  * If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, please contact us directly at support@toovia.com. 

How you can access your information:

  * Update your account at any time by logging in and changing your TOOVIA Profile.
  * Unsubscribe from email communications from us by clicking on the "unsubscribe link" provided in such communications. As noted above, you may not opt out of Service-related communications (e.g.: account verification, purchase and billing confirmations, and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Service, and technical and security notices).
  * If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, please contact us directly at support@toovia.com. 

> 6\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

TOOVIA does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone below the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Service. The Service and its content are not directed at children below the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child below the age of 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child below the age of 13, please contact us at legal@toovia.com.

> 7\. OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES

We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our Service, including the information or content contained within them. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Service to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to those third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on TOOVIA, are subject to that third party's own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and do not have control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service and you allow them to access your User Content you do so at your own risk. 

> 8\. HOW TO CONTACT US ABOUT A DECEASED USERS

In the event of the death of TOOVIA User, please send us an email to the following email address: support@toovia.com. We will usually conduct our communication via email; should we require any other information, we will contact you at the email address you have provided in your request. 

> 9\. HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please contact us at support@toovia.com. 

> 10\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

TOOVIA may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically. We may provide you additional forms of notice of modifications or updates as appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of TOOVIA or the Service after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification. 

{"$type":"planner.model.TUserPageContext","$version":0,"$uri":"mem://planner.model.ejt.TListPageViewImpl@771370375.PageContext-866573598524964874"}
